University of Connecticut, Provost's Office Records 1989.0003
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series II: General Correspondence [Albert E. Waugh], 1950-1965
  - Institutes
    - Public Service (Box 5:, Folder 224-227)
    - Urban Research (Box 5:, Folder 228-229)
    - Water Resources (Box 5:, Folder 230)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 5:, Folder 231-233)
  - J (Box 5:, Folder 234)
  - Jorgensen, President: 25th Anniversary (Box 5:, Folder 235-237)
  - Jorgensen, A.N. (Box 5:, Folder 238-240)
  - Jorgensen: President's Anniversary Celebration (Box 5:, Folder 241-245)
  - K (Box 5:, Folder 246-247)
  - L (Box 5:, Folder 248-252)
  - Labor Education, Center for (Box 5:, Folder 253-256)
  - Labor Management Institute (Box 5:, Folder 257-260)
  - Law, School of (Box 5:, Folder 261-264)
  - Law (Box 5:, Folder 265)
  - Legislative Material to 1960 (Box 6:, Folder 266-269)
  - Liaison Committee, 1957-1962 (Box 7:, Folder 270-272)
  - Library (Box 7:, Folder 273-279)
  - Library Sub-Committee, 1950 (Box 7:, Folder 280)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1964 (Box 7:, Folder 281-288)
  - M (Box 7:, Folder 289-290)
  - Marine Research Lab (Box 7:, Folder 291-297)
  - Medical Technology Program (Box 7:, Folder 298)
  - Medicine, School of (Box 7:, Folder 299)
  - Medicine: School of Dentistry (Box 7:, Folder 300)
  - Medical/Dental/Veterinary (Box 7:, Folder 301-303)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 7:, Folder 304)
  - N (Box 7:, Folder 305-308)
  - National Defense Training, Division of (Box 7:, Folder 309-311)
  - Nursing (Box 7:, Folder 312)
  - O (Box 7:, Folder 313)
  - P (Box 7:, Folder 314-318)
  - Parking (Box 8:, Folder 319-323)
  - Personnel (Box 8:, Folder 324)
  - Pharmacy (Box 8:, Folder 325)
  - Physical Education (Box 8:, Folder 326)
  - Physical Therapy (Box 8:, Folder 327)
  - Planetarium (Box 8:, Folder 328-329)
  - Positions (Box 8:, Folder 330)
  - President, New (Box 8:, Folder 331)
  - Provost's Council (Box 8:, Folder 332)
  - Publications (Box 8:, Folder 333)
  - Q (Box 8:, Folder 334)
  - R (Box 8:, Folder 335-339)
  - Radio and T.V. Center (Box 8:, Folder 340-342)
  - Reading Improvement Program (Box 8:, Folder 343)
  - Reappointment, Promotion and Tenure, 1959-1962 (Box 8:, Folder 344-353)
  - Registrar (Box 8:, Folder 354-358)
  - Religion (Box 8:, Folder 359)
  - Religious Education, 1941 (Box 8:, Folder 360)
  - Retirement (Box 8:, Folder 361-362)
  - Riccio, Leonard C. (Box 8:, Folder 363-366)
  - S (Box 9:, Folder 367-374)
  - Security (Box 9:, Folder 375-376)
  - Senate Committee: Recognition of retiring staff (Box 9:, Folder 377)
  - Sigma Chi (Box 9:, Folder 378)
  - Social Work (Box 9:, Folder 379-380)
  - Speaking Engagements (Box 9:, Folder 381)
  - State Departments of Education (Box 9:, Folder 382-383)
  - State Personnel Department (Box 9:, Folder 384)
  - Student Personnel (Box 9:, Folder 385)
  - T (Box 9:, Folder 386-388)
  - Teaching Loads (Box 9:, Folder 389-392)
  - Teaching Loads: Committee to Study, 1951-1952 (Box 9:, Folder 393-394)
  - Technical Service Act (Box 9:, Folder 395-396)
  - Trustee Faculty Administration Committee (Box 9:, Folder 397)
  - U (Box 9:, Folder 398)
  - UConn 25th Anniversary (Box 9:, Folder 399)
  - University Research Institute of Connecticut (URIC) (Box 9:, Folder 400)
  - University Senate, 1959-1965 (Box 9:, Folder 401-403)
  - University Shop (Box 9:, Folder 404-405)
  - V (Box 9:, Folder 406)
  - Visiting Lecturers (Box 9:, Folder 407)
  - W (Box 9:, Folder 408-412)
  - Waugh, A.E., 1955-1958 (Box 9:, Folder 413-418)
  - X - Y (Box 9:, Folder 419)
  - Z (Box 9:, Folder 420)
- Series III: General Correspondence [Edward V. Gant], 1965-1974
  - A (Box 10:, Folder 421-423)
  - Academy for Educational Development, 1970-1971 (Box 10:, Folder 424-426)
  - Accrediting (Box 10:, Folder 427)
  - Accreditation, 1970-1971 (Box 10:, Folder 428)
  - Admissions (Box 10:, Folder 429)
  - Admissions, 1970-1971 (Box 10:, Folder 430-431)
  - Agreements and Contracts (Box 10:, Folder 432)
  - Alumni Association (Box 10:, Folder 433-437)
  - Allowance Representation: Alumni Association (Box 10:, Folder 438-439)
  - A.A.U.P. (Box 10:, Folder 440-442)
  - American Council on Education (Box 10:, Folder 443-435)
  - American Cyanamid Co. (Box 10:, Folder 436-437)
  - American Society of Civil Engineers (Box 10:, Folder 438)
  - Animal Facilities (Box 10:, Folder 439-440)
  - Anton Case, 1972-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 441)
  - Applications: Staff (Box 10:, Folder 442-444)
  - Architectural education: articles (Box 10:, Folder 445)
  - Architecture Department: Proposal and reports (Box 10:, Folder 446-448)
  - Association of American Colleges (Box 10:, Folder 449-451)
  - ASCUS (Box 10:, Folder 452)
  - Asylum Avenue Property (1280) (Box 10:, Folder 453)
  - Auditorium (Box 10:, Folder 454-457)
  - Avery Point clippings (Box 10:, Folder 458-460)
  - B (Box 11:, Folder 461-464)
  - Babbidge, Homer D. (Box 11:, Folder 465-468)
  - Bartlett Arboretum (Box 11:, Folder 469-471)
  - Budget Material (Box 11:, Folder 472)
  - Budget (Box 11:, Folder 473)
  - Bulletin Board (Box 11:, Folder 474)
  - By-laws (Box 11:, Folder 475)
  - C (Box 11:, Folder 476-479)
  - Calendar U.C., 1971-1972 (Box 11:, Folder 480)
  - Capitol Building Projects (Box 11:, Folder 481-486)
  - Catalog (Box 11:, Folder 487-489)
  - Center for Animal Care (Box 11:, Folder 490)
  - Center for Black Studies (Box 11:, Folder 491-495)
  - Center for Italian Studies (Box 11:, Folder 496-498)
  - Center for Real Estate and Urban Economic Studies (Box 11:, Folder 499-501)
  - Central Naugatuck Valley Regional Education News (Box 11:, Folder 502)
  - Civil Rights Liberties (Box 11:, Folder 503-504)
  - Classified Positions (Box 11:, Folder 505-506)
  - Clerical Positions (Box 11:, Folder 507)
  - Clinical Psychology (Box 11:, Folder 508)
  - Commencement (Box 12:, Folder 509-512)
  - Commencement citations (Box 12:, Folder 513)
  - Community Colleges (Box 12:, Folder 514-515)
  - Computer Center (Box 12:, Folder 516-518)
  - Connfacts (Box 12:, Folder 519-520)
  - Conferences and Institutes (Box 12:, Folder 521)
  - Connpep (Box 12:, Folder 522-524)
  - Connecticut Research Commission (Box 12:, Folder 525-526)
  - CT State Department of Education (Box 12:, Folder 527)
  - Conntac (Box 12:, Folder 528-531)
  - Consulting (Box 12:, Folder 532-533)
  - Continuing Education Services (Box 12:, Folder 534)
  - Controller (Box 12:, Folder 535-537)
  - Counseling (Box 12:, Folder 538)
  - Counselor to Provost (Box 12:, Folder 539)
  - Cremator (Box 12:, Folder 540)
  - Criminal Justice Program (Box 12:, Folder 541)
  - D (Box 12:, Folder 542)
  - Danforth Foundation (Box 12:, Folder 543-535)
  - Data processing (Box 12:, Folder 536-537)
  - D.A.T.P. (Box 12:, Folder 538)
  - Disciplinary Action (Box 12:, Folder 539)
  - Draft (Box 12:, Folder 540)
  - Drugs: use and abuse (Box 12:, Folder 541)
  - Dunham Memorial Carrillon (Box 12:, Folder 542)
  - E (Box 12:, Folder 543)
  - Educom (Box 12:, Folder 544-547)
  - Electron Microscopy, 1968-1972 (Box 13:, Folder 548)
  - Emeritus Staff (Box 13:, Folder 549)
  - Environmental Health Program (Box 13:, Folder 550)
  - Environmental Studies (Box 13:, Folder 551-552)
  - Environment and Man, Center for (Box 13:, Folder 553-557)
  - Etherington Report (Box 13:, Folder 558)
  - Equal Opportunities (Box 13:, Folder 559)
  - Evans, John M. (Box 13:, Folder 560)
  - Evans, John M.: office (Box 13:, Folder 561-562)
  - Exercise Exchange (Box 13:, Folder 563)
  - Experimental College (Box 13:, Folder 564)
  - F (Box 13:, Folder 565)
  - Facility clearance (Box 13:, Folder 566)
  - Faculty Center (Box 13:, Folder 567-568)
  - Faculty-Children Plan (Box 13:, Folder 569-572)
  - Faculty Evaluation (Box 13:, Folder 573-574)
  - Faculty Summer Fellowships (Box 13:, Folder 575)
  - Federation of University Teachers (Box 13:, Folder 576-577)
  - Finance and Control Committee (Box 13:, Folder 578-579)
  - Fiscal Autonomy (Box 13:, Folder 580)
  - Flying Club (Box 13:, Folder 581)
  - Foreign Student and Services (Box 13:, Folder 582)
  - “Freeze, The” (Box 13:, Folder 583)
  - G (Box 13:, Folder 584)
  - Gall, Galvin G. (Box 13:, Folder 585)
  - Gant, E. (Box 13:, Folder 586-590)
  - Goodwin, Dorothy (Box 13:, Folder 591)
  - Governor's Executive Orders (Box 14:, Folder 592)
  - Grant Applications (Box 14:, Folder 593-595)
  - Gulley Hall (Box 14:, Folder 596)
  - H (Box 14:, Folder 597)
  - Hampton Institute (Box 14:, Folder 598-599)
  - Hartford, John Foundation (Box 14:, Folder 600)
  - Hartford Seminary Foundation (Box 14:, Folder 601)
  - Haskins Laboratory (Box 14:, Folder 602)
  - Health, Education and Welfare (Box 14:, Folder 603-605)
  - H.E.W. Grants (Box 14:, Folder 606-607)
  - Health Services (Box 14:, Folder 608-613)
  - Higher Education (Box 14:, Folder 614-625)
  - Higher Education: Community Service (Box 14:, Folder 626-627)
  - Higher Education
    - Title I (Box 14:, Folder 628)
    - Title II (Box 14:, Folder 629)
    - Title VI (Box 14:, Folder 630-631)
    - Title VI A (Box 14:, Folder 632)
  - Honorariums (Box 15:, Folder 633)
  - Honors Program: GSR (Box 15:, Folder 634-638)
  - Housing (Box 15:, Folder 639-640)
  - Human Development Studies Group (Box 15:, Folder 641)
  - Human rights and opportunities (Box 15:, Folder 642-648)
  - I (Box 15:, Folder 649)
  - Information Services (Box 15:, Folder 650)
  - Inner College Experiment (Box 15:, Folder 651-655)
  - Institutes
    - Cellular Biology (Box 15:, Folder 656)
    - Corrections (Box 15:, Folder 657)
    - For the Future (Box 15:, Folder 658)
    - International and Intercultural Studies (Box 15:, Folder 659-662)
    - Marine Sciences (Box 15:, Folder 663-666)
    - Materials Sciences (Box 15:, Folder 667-668)
    - Nutrition and Food Sciences (Box 16:, Folder 669-670)
    - Public Service (Box 16:, Folder 671-674)
  - Institutional Research, Bureau of (Box 16:, Folder 675-681)
  - Institute of Urban Research (Box 16:, Folder 682-684)
  - Institute of Water Resources (Box 16:, Folder 685-687)
  - Insurance (Box 16:, Folder 688)
  - Interuniversity Comm. Council: Minutes (Box 16:, Folder 689-690)
  - J (Box 16:, Folder 691)
  - K (Box 16:, Folder 692)
  - K.O. material (Box 16:, Folder 693)
  - Kitchen Kabinet (Box 16:, Folder 694)
  - L (Box 16:, Folder 695)
  - Labor Education (Box 16:, Folder 696)
  - Labor Education Center (Box 16:, Folder 697-699)
  - Land Grant Universities (Box 16:, Folder 700-701)
  - Latin American History (Box 16:, Folder 702-703)
  - Legislative Material (Box 16:, Folder 704-707)
  - Library (Box 17:, Folder 708-714)
  - Loeb Awards (Box 17:, Folder 715)
  - Long Island Bridge Study (Box 17:, Folder 716-717)
  - Long Range Planning Committee (Box 17:, Folder 718-719)
  - M (Box 17:, Folder 720-722)
  - Management Council (Box 17:, Folder 723)
  - Marine Research Laboratory (Box 17:, Folder 724)
  - Mass Spectrometer (Box 17:, Folder 725)
  - Mental Health, Board of (Box 17:, Folder 726-727)
  - Men's Faculty Club (Box 17:, Folder 728)
  - Meskill's (Governor) memos (Box 17:, Folder 739-730)
  - Microfilm supplies (Box 17:, Folder 731)
  - Microwave-closed circuit T.V. systems (Box 17:, Folder 732)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 17:, Folder 733)
  - Monograph and Occasional Paper Series (Box 17:, Folder 734)
  - Motor Vehicle Safety and Control (Box 17:, Folder 735-736)
  - N (Box 17:, Folder 737)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges (Box 17:, Folder 738-740)
  - National Patent Development Corp. (Box 17:, Folder 741)
  - National Science Foundation (Box 17:, Folder 742-743)
  - Nature Conservancy (Box 17:, Folder 744)
  - N.E. Association of College and Secondary Schools (Box 17:, Folder 745-747)
  - N.E. Board of Higher Education (Box 17:, Folder 748)
  - New England Center for Continuing Education (Box 18:, Folder 749-760)
  - New England Regional Computing Program (Box 18:, Folder 761)
  - New Haven/Hamden/Quinnipiac Project (Box 18:, Folder 762)
  - Newspaper clippings (Box 18:, Folder 763-769)
  - O (Box 18:, Folder 770)
  - Office of Research Development (Box 18:, Folder 771)
  - Oral History Project (Box 18:, Folder 772-773)
  - Orr, William: correspondence (Box 18:, Folder 774)
  - P (Box 18:, Folder 775)
  - Parking (Box 18:, Folder 776)
  - Personnel (Box 18:, Folder 777-779)
  - Physical plant requests (Box 19:, Folder 780-781)
  - Placement (Box 19:, Folder 782-785)
  - Planetarium (Box 19:, Folder 786)
  - Positions (Box 19:, Folder 787-788)
  - President's Newsletter (Box 19:, Folder 789-790)
  - President Search Committee (Box 19:, Folder 791)
  - Project Leadership (Box 19:, Folder 792)
  - Provost's Council (Box 19:, Folder 793-796)
  - Provost's Employment: secretaries (Box 19:, Folder 797)
  - Provost's office equipment (Box 19:, Folder 798)
  - Office of Publications (Box 19:, Folder 799)
  - Public Information and Publications (Box 19:, Folder 800)
  - Public information, Office of (Box 19:, Folder 801-802)
  - Public Relations: Moreland (Box 19:, Folder 803-804)
  - Public Safety (Box 19:, Folder 805)
  - Public Works (Box 19:, Folder 806)
  - Purchasing (Box 19:, Folder 807)
  - Personnel: Questionnaires concerning Blacks (Box 19:, Folder 808)
  - R (Box 19:, Folder 809)
  - Radio and TV Center (Box 19:, Folder 810-811)
  - Radio and TV Center News (Box 19:, Folder 812-813)
  - Reading Improvement Program (Box 19:, Folder 814)
  - Registrar (Box 19:, Folder 815-818)
  - Religion (Box 19:, Folder 819-821)
  - Retired Professor's Registry (Box 20:, Folder 822)
  - Retirement (Box 20:, Folder 823)
  - Ribicoff Center (Box 20:, Folder 824)
  - Rosenberg, William A. (Box 20:, Folder 825)
  - S (Box 20:, Folder 826)
  - Sabbatic Leaves (Box 20:, Folder 827-828)
  - Sea Grant Program (Box 20:, Folder 829)
  - Security (Box 20:, Folder 830-831)
  - Shopping Center (Box 20:, Folder 832)
  - Smoking (Box 20:, Folder 833-834)
  - Social Science Data Center (Box 20:, Folder 835-837)
  - Space Seminar (Box 20:, Folder 838)
  - Star Report: Law School (Box 20:, Folder 839)
  - Storrs Grammar School (Box 20:, Folder 840)
  - Surplus Equipment (Box 20:, Folder 841)
  - T (Box 20:, Folder 842)
  - Technical Services Act (Box 20:, Folder 843)
  - Technical Services Center (Box 20:, Folder 844-845)
  - Tenure, reappointment, and promotion (Box 20:, Folder 846-847)
  - Thirties Program (Box 20:, Folder 848)
  - Torrington Company (Box 20:, Folder 849)
  - Travel (Box 20:, Folder 850-855)
  - Tropical Studies Organization (Box 20:, Folder 856-858)
  - Tuitions (Box 20:, Folder 859-860)
  - TV's: Faculty Center (Box 20:, Folder 861-862)
  - Typewriters (Box 20:, Folder 863)
  - U (Box 21:, Folder 864)
  - University Attorney (Box 21:, Folder 865)
  - University of Connecticut Foundation, Inc. (Box 21:, Folder 866)
  - University Ombudsman (Box 21:, Folder 867)
  - University Shop (Box 21:, Folder 868)
  - Upward Bound Program (Box 21:, Folder 869)
  - Urban Semester (Box 21:, Folder 870-871)
  - V (Box 21:, Folder 872)
  - Veterinary Medicine (Box 21:, Folder 873)
  - Vice President, K.G. Wilson (Box 21:, Folder 874)
  - Vietnam Moratorium (Box 21:, Folder 875)
  - Violence, Study of (Box 21:, Folder 876)
  - Virgin Island, College of (Box 21:, Folder 877-881)
  - Visiting Professors (Box 21:, Folder 882-883)
  - Vouchers
    - Book orders (Box 21:, Folder 884-885)
    - Microfilm (Box 21:, Folder 886)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 21:, Folder 887-888)
    - Office Supplies (Box 21:, Folder 889-890)
    - Travel Interviews (Box 21:, Folder 891)
    - Visiting Lecturers Series: Alumni Association (Box 21:, Folder 892)
  - W (Box 21:, Folder 893)
  - WHUS (Box 21:, Folder 894)
- Series IV: Schools and Colleges, 1948-1971
  - Subseries A: 1948-1965
    - Accounting (Box 22:, Folder 895)
    - Business (Box 22:, Folder 896)
    - Industrial Administration (Box 22:, Folder 897)
    - Marketing (Box 22:, Folder 898)
    - School of Education (Box 22:, Folder 899-909)
      - Educational Research and Testing (Box 22:, Folder 910)
      - Audio-Visual Center (Box 22:, Folder 911)
      - Cooperative Program for Superior Students (Box 22:, Folder 912)
      - Edwin O. Smith High School (Box 22:, Folder 913-914)
    - School of Engineering (Box 22:, Folder 915-919)
    - School of Engineering (Box 23:, Folder 920-922)
      - Aeronautical (Box 23:, Folder 923)
      - Biological (Box 23:, Folder 924)
      - Chemical (Box 23:, Folder 925)
      - Civil (Box 23:, Folder 926)
      - Electrical (Box 23:, Folder 927)
      - Mechanical (Box 23:, Folder 928)
      - Nuclear (Box 23:, Folder 929)
    - Fine Arts, School of (Box 23:, Folder 930-931)
      - Architecture (Box 23:, Folder 932)
      - Art (Box 23:, Folder 933)
      - Art Museum (Box 23:, Folder 934)
      - Music (Box 23:, Folder 935)
      - Theatre (Box 23:, Folder 936)
    - Graduate School (Box 23:, Folder 937-940)
  - Subseries B: 1966-1968
    - Agriculture, College of (Box 23:, Folder 941)
      - Agricultural Economics (Box 23:, Folder 942)
      - Agricultural Engineering (Box 23:, Folder 943)
      - Agricultural Experiment Station (Box 23:, Folder 944)
      - Animal Diseases (Box 23:, Folder 945)
      - Animal Genetics (Box 23:, Folder 946)
      - Animal Industries (Box 23:, Folder 947)
      - Plant Science (Box 23:, Folder 948)
      - Polutry Science (Box 23:, Folder 949)
      - Rural Sociology (Box 23:, Folder 950)
      - Ratcliffe Hicks (Box 23:, Folder 951)
    - Arts and Sciences (Box 23:, Folder 952-953)
      - Bacteriology (Box 23:, Folder 954)
      - Biological Sciences Group (Box 23:, Folder 955)
      - Botany (Box 23:, Folder 956)
      - Chemistry (Box 23:, Folder 957)
      - Economics (Box 23:, Folder 958)
      - English (Box 23:, Folder 959)
      - Foreign Languages (Box 23:, Folder 960)
      - Genetics (Box 23:, Folder 961)
      - Geology (Box 23:, Folder 962)
      - Germanic and Slavic Languages (Box 23:, Folder 963)
      - History (Box 23:, Folder 964)
      - Journalism (Box 23:, Folder 965)
      - Linguistics (Box 23:, Folder 966)
      - Mathematics (Box 24:, Folder 967)
      - National Defense (Box 24:, Folder 968)
      - Natural Sciences (Box 24:, Folder 969)
      - Philosophy (Box 24:, Folder 970)
      - Physics (Box 24:, Folder 971)
      - Political Science (Box 24:, Folder 972)
      - Psychology (Box 24:, Folder 973)
      - Romance and Classical Languages (Box 24:, Folder 974)
      - Speech and Drama (Box 24:, Folder 975)
      - Sociology and Anthropology (Box 24:, Folder 976)
      - Statistics (Box 24:, Folder 977)
      - Zoology (Box 24:, Folder 978)
    - Business Administration (Box 24:, Folder 979)
      - Accounting (Box 24:, Folder 980)
      - Business Law (Box 24:, Folder 981)
      - Finance (Box 24:, Folder 982)
      - Industrial Administration (Box 24:, Folder 983)
      - Insurance (Box 24:, Folder 984)
      - Marketing (Box 24:, Folder 985)
      - NERAC (Box 24:, Folder 986)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 24:, Folder 987)
    - Education, School of (Box 25:, Folder 988-989)
      - Audio-visual Aids (Box 25:, Folder 990)
      - Co-op Program for Superior Students (Box 25:, Folder 991)
      - Educational Research (Box 25:, Folder 992)
      - E.O. Smith High School (Box 25:, Folder 993)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 25:, Folder 994-996)
      - Aeronautical (Box 25:, Folder 997)
      - Biological (Box 25:, Folder 998)
      - Chemical (Box 25:, Folder 999)
      - Civil (Box 25:, Folder 1000)
      - Electrical (Box 25:, Folder 1001)
      - Experiment Station (Box 25:, Folder 1002)
      - Mechanical (Box 25:, Folder 1003)
      - Metallurgy, Department of (Box 25:, Folder 1004)
    - Fine Arts, School of (Box 25:, Folder 1005)
      - Architecture (Box 25:, Folder 1006)
      - Art (Box 25:, Folder 1007)
      - Art Museum (Box 25:, Folder 1008)
      - Music (Box 25:, Folder 1009)
      - Theatre (Box 25:, Folder 1010)
    - Graduate School (Box 25:, Folder 1011)
      - Research Foundation (Box 25:, Folder 1012-1013)
    - Health Center (Box 25:, Folder 1014)
    - Home Economics, School of (Box 25:, Folder 1015)
      - Child Development and Family Relations (Box 25:, Folder 1016)
      - Clothing, Textile and Related Art (Box 25:, Folder 1017)
      - Foods and Nutrition (Box 25:, Folder 1018)
      - Home Management (Box 25:, Folder 1019)
    - Law School (Box 26:, Folder 1020-1021)
    - Medicine, School of (Box 26:, Folder 1022)
    - Nursing, School of/School of Physical Therapy (Box 26:, Folder 1023-1024)
    - Pharmacy, School of (Box 26:, Folder 1025)
    - Physical Education, School of (Box 26:, Folder 1026)
      - Intercollegiate Athletics (Box 26:, Folder 1027)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 26:, Folder 1028-1029)
  - Subseries C: 1968-1969
    - Branches
      - At other colleges (Box 26:, Folder 1030)
      - Hartford (Box 26:, Folder 1031)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 26:, Folder 1032)
      - New London: Avery Point (Box 26:, Folder 1033)
      - Stamford (Box 26:, Folder 1034)
      - Torrington (Box 26:, Folder 1035)
      - Waterbury (Box 26:, Folder 1036)
      - T.V. (Box 26:, Folder 1037)
      - Personnel (Box 26:, Folder 1038)
      - Positions (Box 26:, Folder 1039)
      - Sub-Committee (Box 26:, Folder 1040)
    - Agriculture, College of (Box 27:, Folder 1041)
      - Agricultural Economics (Box 27:, Folder 1042)
      - Agricultural Engineering (Box 27:, Folder 1043)
      - Agricultural Experiment Station (Box 27:, Folder 1044)
      - Agricultural Extension (Box 27:, Folder 1045-1046)
      - Animal Disease (Box 27:, Folder 1047)
      - Animal Industries (Box 27:, Folder 1048)
      - Plant Science (Box 27:, Folder 1049)
      - Ratcliffe Hicks (Box 27:, Folder 1050)
      - Rural Sociology (Box 27:, Folder 1051)
    - Arts and Sciences, College of (Box 27:, Folder 1052-1053)
      - Bacteriology (Box 27:, Folder 1054)
      - Biological Sciences Group (Box 27:, Folder 1055)
      - Biobehavioral Sciences (Box 27:, Folder 1056)
      - Chemistry (Box 27:, Folder 1057)
      - Economics (Box 27:, Folder 1058)
      - English (Box 27:, Folder 1059)
      - Geology (Box 27:, Folder 1060)
      - Germanic and Slavic Languages (Box 27:, Folder 1061)
      - History (Box 27:, Folder 1062)
      - Journalism (Box 27:, Folder 1063)
      - Linguistics (Box 27:, Folder 1064)
      - Marine Research Laboratory (Box 27:, Folder 1065)
      - Mathematics (Box 27:, Folder 1066)
      - National Defense (Box 27:, Folder 1067)
      - Philosophy (Box 27:, Folder 1068)
      - Physics (Box 27:, Folder 1069)
      - Psychology (Box 27:, Folder 1070)
      - Political Science (Box 27:, Folder 1071)
      - Romance and Classical Languages (Box 27:, Folder 1072)
      - Speech and Drama (Box 27:, Folder 1073)
      - Sociology and Anthropology (Box 27:, Folder 1074)
      - Statistics (Box 27:, Folder 1075)
      - Zoology (Box 27:, Folder 1076)
    - Business Administration (Box 27:, Folder 1077-1078)
      - Accounting (Box 27:, Folder 1079)
      - Finance (Box 27:, Folder 1080)
      - Industrial Administration (Box 27:, Folder 1081)
      - Insurance (Box 27:, Folder 1082)
      - Marketing (Box 27:, Folder 1083)
      - MBA Program (Box 27:, Folder 1084)
      - NERAC (Box 27:, Folder 1085)
    - Education, School of (Box 28:, Folder 1086)
      - Audio-Visual Aids (Box 28:, Folder 1087)
      - Co-op Program for Superior Students (Box 28:, Folder 1088)
      - Educational Research (Box 28:, Folder 1089)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 28:, Folder 1090)
      - Aeronautical Engineering (Box 28:, Folder 1091)
      - Biological Engineering (Box 28:, Folder 1092)
      - Chemical Engineering (Box 28:, Folder 1093)
      - Civil Engineering (Box 28:, Folder 1094)
      - Electrical Engineering (Box 28:, Folder 1095)